Guide to the Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Awareness Program records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Awareness Program records
1988-2000
1997-2000
SC0945
Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Awareness Program
Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Community Center (Stanford, Calif.)
3.75 Linear feet
Collection consists largely of the evaluation forms completed by students at Bay Area high schools and colleges following a presentation; other records include training manuals, speakers’ resources, and clippings.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
The Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Awareness Program, formed in 1985, worked to end intolerance and stereotypes of lesbian, gay and bisexual persons. Representatives from the group gave presentations to school classes and answered questions. At the time these records were generated, the group was affiliated with the Billy DeFrank Lesbian and Gay Community Center in San Jose, California.
Description of the Collection
Collection consists largely of the evaluation forms completed by students at Bay Area high schools and colleges following a presentation; other records include training manuals, speakers’ resources, and clippings.
Access Terms
Howton, Elizabeth; Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Awareness Program; Gays --California --Public opinion.; Homosexuality --California --Public opinion.
Collection Contents
- Records, Accession ARCH-1998-309
  - Evaluations-Aragon HS, 4/23/1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Evaluations-Carlmont HS, 5/22/1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Evaluations-De Anza College, 10/27/1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Evaluations-De Anza College, 11/3/1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Evaluations-De Anza College, 2/4-2/5/1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Evaluations-De Anza College, 5/12/1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Evaluations-De Anza College, 7/15/1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Evaluations-Del Mar HS, 4/4/1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Evaluations-Gavilan College, 3/26/1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Evaluations-Institute of Transpersonal Psychology, 2/12/1998 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Evaluations-Los Altos United Methodist Church, Stephen Ministry, 4/27/1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Evaluations-Menlo HS, 11/10/1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Evaluations-Menlo HS, 12/19/1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Evaluations-Menlo HS, 2/23/1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Evaluations-Menlo HS, 3/19/1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Evaluations-Menlo HS, 5/11/1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Evaluations-Mission Junior College, 3/18/1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Evaluations-Palo Alto HS, 1/6/1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Evaluations-Palo Alto HS, 4/28-4/30/1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Evaluations-Prospect HS, 4/21/1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Evaluations-San Jose State University, 10/1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Evaluations-San Jose State University, 11/5/1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Evaluations-San Jose State University, 2/1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Evaluations-San Jose State University, 3/1998 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Evaluations-Saratoga HS, 2/23/1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Evaluations-Skyline College, 4/3/1998 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Evaluations-Skyline College, 11/17/1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Evaluations-Terra Nova HS, 1/16/1998 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Evaluations-Woodside HS, 1/15/1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Evaluations-Woodside HS, 1/16/1998 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Evaluations-West Valley College, 1/28/1998 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Evaluations-West Valley College, 2/26/1998 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Evaluations-West Valley College, 4/1998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Evaluations-Woodside HS, 5/28/1998 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Evaluations-Woodside HS, 5/29/1998 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - LGBAP Organization Pamphlets (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Training Manuals (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - LGBAP Speaker’s Resources (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - LGBAP Speaker’s Information (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - LGBAP Training Program (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Coming Out Resources (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Training (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Peninsula Gay and Lesbian Youth Group (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Community United Against Violence Resources. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Training Session Info (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Clippings and articles, 1989-1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Training (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Anything That Moves: Beyond the Myths of Bisexuality, Spring 1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Resources, 1988-1995 and undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Records, Accession ARCH-2000-077
  - Evaluations-Aragon HS, 1/4/2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Evaluations-College of Notre Dame, 4/15/2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Evaluations-De Anza College, 2/2/2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Evaluations-Del Mar HS, 4/20/2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Evaluations-Menlo Atherton HS, 5/28/2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Evaluations-Menlo School, 4/3/2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Evaluations-Sacred Heart Preparatory, 3/2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Evaluations-SJSU, 2/2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Evaluations-SJSU, 3/2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Evaluations-Skyline College, 4/2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Evaluations-Universalist Unitarian Fellowship of Sunnyvale, 2/10/2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Evaluations-West Valley College, 2/10/2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Evaluations-West Valley College, 3/21/2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Evaluations-West Valley College, 5/1/2000 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Evaluations-Woodside HS, 1/2000 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Evaluations-Woodside HS, 5/31/2000 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Evaluations-College of Notre Dame, 12/5/1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Evaluations-De Anza College, 10/26/1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Evaluations-Gavilan College, 10/21/1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Evaluations-Menlo HS, 10/11/1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Evaluations-Menlo School, 11/8/1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Evaluations-Mission College, 10/20/1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Evaluations-Mountain View HS, 10/26/1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Evaluations-SJSU, 10/20/1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Evaluations-SJSU, 9/1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Evaluations-SJSU, 10/19/1999 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Evaluations-Santa Clara University, 11/4/1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Evaluations-Skyline College, 11/1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Evaluations-West Valley College, 9/16/1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Evaluations-West Valley College, 12/1/1999 (Box 2, Folder 14)